[
  {
    "Problem": "Two Sum",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Two%20Sum",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 35877,
    "Dislikes": 1138,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Substring Without Repeating Characters",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Longest%20Substring%20Without%20Repeating%20Characters",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 27270,
    "Dislikes": 1176,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Palindromic Substring",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Longest%20Palindromic%20Substring",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 20445,
    "Dislikes": 1176,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Container With Most Water",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/container-with-most-water",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Container%20With%20Most%20Water",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 19034,
    "Dislikes": 1032,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "3 Sum",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/3sum",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/3Sum",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 20600,
    "Dislikes": 1934,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Remove Nth Node From End of List",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Remove%20Nth%20Node%20From%20End%20of%20List",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Linked List",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 11622,
    "Dislikes": 523,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Valid Parentheses",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Valid%20Parentheses",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 14730,
    "Dislikes": 715,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Merge Two Sorted Lists",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-two-sorted-lists",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Merge%20Two%20Sorted%20Lists",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Linked List",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 13920,
    "Dislikes": 1251,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Merge k Sorted Lists",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-k-sorted-lists",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Heap",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "Like": 13453,
    "Dislikes": 513,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Search in Rotated Sorted Array",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 16470,
    "Dislikes": 1004,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Combination Sum",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Combination%20Sum",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 12607,
    "Dislikes": 260,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Rotate Image",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-image",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Rotate%20Image",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Matrix",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10667,
    "Dislikes": 537,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Group Anagrams",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/group-anagrams",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/blob/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Group%20Anagrams/solution.cpp",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10887,
    "Dislikes": 348,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Maximum Subarray",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Maximum%20Subarray",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 23619,
    "Dislikes": 1129,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Spiral Matrix",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/spiral-matrix",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Spiral%20Matrix",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Matrix",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 8281,
    "Dislikes": 889,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Jump Game",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Jump%20Game",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 12374,
    "Dislikes": 665,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Merge Intervals",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-intervals",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Merge%20Intervals",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Interval",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 15305,
    "Dislikes": 554,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Insert Interval",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/insert-interval",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/blob/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Insert%20Interval/solution.cpp",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Interval",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 5536,
    "Dislikes": 378,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Unique Paths",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-paths",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/blob/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Unique%20Paths/solution.cpp",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 11132,
    "Dislikes": 333,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Climbing Stairs",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/climbing-stairs",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Climbing%20Stairs",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 13508,
    "Dislikes": 402,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Set Matrix Zeroes",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/set-matrix-zeroes",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/blob/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Set%20Matrix%20Zeroes/solution.cpp",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Matrix",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 8476,
    "Dislikes": 531,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Minimum Window Substring",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-window-substring",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "Like": 11600,
    "Dislikes": 553,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Word Search",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Word%20Search",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Matrix",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10364,
    "Dislikes": 389,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Decode Ways",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/decode-ways",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 7605,
    "Dislikes": 3942,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Validate Binary Search Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 11157,
    "Dislikes": 951,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Same Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Same%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 6618,
    "Dislikes": 149,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Binary Tree Level Order Traversal",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Binary%20Tree%20Level%20Order%20Traversal",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10067,
    "Dislikes": 193,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Maximum Depth of Binary Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Maximum%20Depth%20of%20Binary%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 7948,
    "Dislikes": 136,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Construct Binary Tree from Preorder and Inorder Traversal",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10447,
    "Dislikes": 280,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 18675,
    "Dislikes": 599,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Binary Tree Maximum Path Sum",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "Like": 10844,
    "Dislikes": 573,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Valid Palindrome",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-palindrome",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Valid%20Palindrome",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 4406,
    "Dislikes": 5738,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Consecutive Sequence",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-consecutive-sequence",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 12426,
    "Dislikes": 523,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Clone Graph",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/clone-graph",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 6422,
    "Dislikes": 2705,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Word Break",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-break",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 11671,
    "Dislikes": 503,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Linked List Cycle",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Linked%20List%20Cycle",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Linked List",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 9314,
    "Dislikes": 848,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Reorder List",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/reorder-list",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Linked List",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 6745,
    "Dislikes": 233,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Maximum Product Subarray",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-subarray",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 12955,
    "Dislikes": 392,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Find Minimum in Rotated Sorted Array",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-minimum-in-rotated-sorted-array",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 7876,
    "Dislikes": 416,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Reverse Bits",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-bits",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Binary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 3409,
    "Dislikes": 881,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Number of 1 Bits",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-1-bits",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Binary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 3964,
    "Dislikes": 890,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "House Robber",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/House%20Robber",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 13837,
    "Dislikes": 285,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Number of Islands",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-islands",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Number%20of%20Islands",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 15411,
    "Dislikes": 362,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Reverse Linked List",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Reverse%20Linked%20List",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Linked List",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 13711,
    "Dislikes": 237,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Course Schedule",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10678,
    "Dislikes": 420,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Implement Trie (Prefix Tree)",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-trie-prefix-tree",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Design Add and Search Words Data Structure",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/design-add-and-search-words-data-structure",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 5237,
    "Dislikes": 262,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Word Search II",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search-ii",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "Like": 6491,
    "Dislikes": 270,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "House Robber II",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber-ii",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/House%20Robber%20II",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 6432,
    "Dislikes": 101,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Contains Duplicate",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/contains-duplicate",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Contains%20Duplicate",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 5968,
    "Dislikes": 996,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Invert Binary Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/invert-binary-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Invert%20Binary%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 9303,
    "Dislikes": 132,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Kth Smallest Element in a BST",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 7882,
    "Dislikes": 137,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Search Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Lowest%20Common%20Ancestor%20of%20a%20Binary%20Search%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 6784,
    "Dislikes": 213,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Lowest%20Common%20Ancestor%20Of%20A%20Binary%20Search%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 11783,
    "Dislikes": 299,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Product of Array Except Self",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/product-of-array-except-self",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Array",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 13820,
    "Dislikes": 794,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Valid Anagram",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/blob/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Valid%20Anagram/solution.cpp",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 6482,
    "Dislikes": 237,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Meeting Rooms",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/meeting-rooms",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Interval",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Meeting Rooms II",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/meeting-rooms-ii",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Interval",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Graph Valid Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/graph-valid-tree",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": "",
    "Dislikes": "",
    "IsPaidOnly": true
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Missing Number",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/missing-number",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Missing%20Number",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Binary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 6856,
    "Dislikes": 2947,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Alien Dictionary",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/alien-dictionary",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Encode and Decode Strings",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/encode-and-decode-strings",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Find Median from Data Stream",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Heap",
    "Difficulty": "Hard",
    "Like": 7766,
    "Dislikes": 140,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Longest%20Increasing%20Subsequence",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 13854,
    "Dislikes": 256,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Coin Change",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 13209,
    "Dislikes": 296,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Number of Connected Components in an Undirected Graph",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-connected-components-in-an-undirected-graph",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "",
    "Like": -1,
    "Dislikes": -1,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Counting Bits",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/counting-bits",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Binary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 7500,
    "Dislikes": 350,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Top K Frequent Elements",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/top-k-frequent-elements",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Heap",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 10402,
    "Dislikes": 402,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Sum of Two Integers",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-two-integers",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Binary",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 2812,
    "Dislikes": 4131,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Pacific Atlantic Water Flow",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/pacific-atlantic-water-flow",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Graph",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 4342,
    "Dislikes": 936,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Repeating Character Replacement",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-repeating-character-replacement",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 5567,
    "Dislikes": 218,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Non-overlapping Intervals",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/non-overlapping-intervals",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Interval",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 4488,
    "Dislikes": 132,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Serialize and Deserialize BST",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-bst",
    "Solution": "#",
    "Status": false,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 2870,
    "Dislikes": 137,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Subtree of Another Tree",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/subtree-of-another-tree",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Subtree%20of%20Another%20Tree",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Tree",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "Like": 5912,
    "Dislikes": 321,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Palindromic Substrings",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindromic-substrings",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/main/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Palindromic%20Substrings",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "String",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 7706,
    "Dislikes": 170,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  },
  {
    "Problem": "Longest Common Subsequence",
    "Question": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-subsequence",
    "Solution": "https://github.com/HarshNarwariya/DSA/tree/master/Blind%2075%20Must%20Do%20Leetcode/Longest%20Common%20Subsequence",
    "Status": true,
    "Tag": "Dynamic Programming",
    "Difficulty": "Medium",
    "Like": 7681,
    "Dislikes": 86,
    "IsPaidOnly": false
  }
]
